Guide to the National Law Center records, 1865-2005 RG0014
Special Collections Research Center, The George Washington University
- Law alumni photographs, 1921-1989; RG0014 Series 13; 7.5 Linear feet (Box 9, Box 8, Box 7, Box 6, Box 13, Box 12, Box 11, Box 10, Box 15, Box 14, Box 1, Box 2, Box 3, Box 4, Box 5)
  - Jacob Burns, Joe Brand and Van Vleck Moot Court, 04/1989 (Box 9, Folder 146.1)
  - Jacob Burns, Joe Brand and Van Vleck Moot Court, 04/1989 (Box 9, Folder 146.11)
  - Jacob Burns, Joe Brand and Van Vleck Moot Court, 04/1989 (Box 9, Folder 146.12)
  - Jacob Burns, Joe Brand and Van Vleck Moot Court, 04/1989 (Box 9, Folder 146.13)
  - Jacob Burns, Joe Brand and Van Vleck Moot Court, 04/1989 (Box 9, Folder 146.14)
  - Jacob Burns, Joe Brand and Van Vleck Moot Court, 04/1989 (Box 9, Folder 146.15)
  - Jacob Burns, Joe Brand and Van Vleck Moot Court, 04/1989 (Box 9, Folder 146.16)
  - Jacob Burns, Joe Brand and Van Vleck Moot Cour, 04/1989 (Box 9, Folder 146.17)
    Sheet of Negatives
  - Deans Shultz, Stanek and Swartz, 1989 (Box 9, Folder 147.1)
    Spring
  - Terrace, 1989 (Box 9, Folder 147.2)
  - Terrace, 1989 (Box 9, Folder 147.3)
  - Woman taking a flash photograph, 1989 (Box 9, Folder 147.4)
  - Man at phone in office, 1989 (Box 9, Folder 147.5)
  - Terrace, 1989 (Box 9, Folder 147.6)
  - Woman at desk holding a book over head, 1989 (Box 9, Folder 147.7)
  - Deans Shultz, Stanek and Swartz, 1989 (Box 9, Folder 147.8)
  - Sheet of Negatives, 1989 (Box 9, Folder 147.9)
  - Men and women at gathering watching and smiling at something, undated (Box 9, Folder 148.1)
  - People atanding and sitting at gathering, undated (Box 9, Folder 148.2)
  - Pres. Trachenberg standing at doorway of gathering, undated (Box 9, Folder 148.3)
  - Pres. Trachenberg at gathering, undated (Box 9, Folder 148.4)
  - Pres. Trachenberg at gathering, undated (Box 9, Folder 148.5)
  - Gathering, undated (Box 9, Folder 148.6)
  - Same gathering as above, undated (Box 9, Folder 148.7)
  - Pres. Trachenberg and another man talking, undated (Box 9, Folder 148.8)
  - Sheet of Negatives, undated (Box 9, Folder 148.9)
  - Two men chatting, undated (Box 9, Folder 149.1)
  - A man in a graduation gown saluting a woman, undated (Box 9, Folder 149.2)
  - A group chatting over refreshments, undated (Box 9, Folder 149.3)
  - Men in grauduation gowns chatting, undated (Box 9, Folder 149.4)
  - Pres. Trachtenberg greeting an unidentified man, undated (Box 9, Folder 149.5)
  - A man in a graduation gown chatting with two women, undated (Box 9, Folder 149.6)
  - A man in a graduation gown chatting with two women, undated (Box 9, Folder 149.7)
  - Three men chatting, undated (Box 9, Folder 149.8)
  - Pres. Trachtenberg talking to a child, undated (Box 9, Folder 149.9)
  - Men in graduation gowns, undated (Box 9, Folder 149.1)
  - Two graduates in graduation gowns, undated (Box 9, Folder 149.11)
  - A group of graduates in gowns, undated (Box 9, Folder 149.12)
  - Three men in graduation gowns, undated (Box 9, Folder 149.13)
  - A gropu of graduates in gowns, undated (Box 9, Folder 149.14)
  - Two men posing for a photo, undated (Box 9, Folder 149.15)
  - A group of graduate, undated (Box 9, Folder 149.16)
  - A group of graduates, undated (Box 9, Folder 149.17)
  - Negatives of prints of folder #149, undated (Box 9, Folder 149.18)
  - Negatives of prints of folder #149, undated (Box 9, Folder 149.19)
  - Negatives of prints of folder #149, undated (Box 9, Folder 149.2)
  - A man and a woman having a conversation, undated (Box 9, Folder 150.1)
  - 2 Men and a woman posing for the camera, undated (Box 9, Folder 150.2)
  - 2 men and 2 women having a conversation, undated (Box 9, Folder 150.3)
  - Two men having a conversation, undated (Box 9, Folder 150.4)
  - A picture of a crowd of people socializing, undated (Box 9, Folder 150.5)
  - Two men and a women socializing, undated (Box 9, Folder 150.6)
  - Two men and a women socializing, undated (Box 9, Folder 150.7)
  - Two men and a women socializing, undated (Box 9, Folder 150.8)
  - Two men and a women socializing, undated (Box 9, Folder 150.9)
  - A woman and two men socializing, undated (Box 9, Folder 150.1)
  - A woman and two men socializing, undated (Box 9, Folder 150.11)
  - 2 Women and 2 men socializing, undated (Box 9, Folder 150.12)
  - A group of people socializing, undated (Box 9, Folder 150.13)
  - A group of people socializing, undated (Box 9, Folder 150.14)
  - 3 Women and a man socializing, undated (Box 9, Folder 150.15)
  - 3 Women and a man socializing, undated (Box 9, Folder 150.16)
  - A woman and a man posing for a picture, undated (Box 9, Folder 150.17)
  - A woman and two men socializing, undated (Box 9, Folder 150.18)
  - Andrei Parastaeu, Susan Medalie, Larry Margolis,Sergei Chetverikov, undated (Box 9, Folder 150.19)
  - Jack Friedenthal, Susan Medalie, Simon Weisenthal, undated (Box 9, Folder 150.2)
  - Picture of a painter of Lenin, undated (Box 9, Folder 150.21)
  - Sandra O'Connor, A. Kennedy, Yuri Dubinin, undated (Box 9, Folder 150.22)
  - Dean Fiedenthaland, Antonio Scalia, undated (Box 9, Folder 150.23)
  - Kennedy, Unknown idividual, Sapir, undated (Box 9, Folder 150.24)
  - Unknown individual, Lawerence Margolis, Scalia, undated (Box 9, Folder 150.25)
  - Two men shaking hands while a woman looks on, undated (Box 9, Folder 151.1)
  - 2 men and 2 women, undated (Box 9, Folder 151.2)
  - 2 men and a woman, undated (Box 9, Folder 151.3)
  - Two men posing for the camera, undated (Box 9, Folder 151.4)
  - Two men shaking hands, undated (Box 9, Folder 151.5)
  - Two men shaking hands, undated (Box 9, Folder 151.6)
  - Two women and two men conversating, undated (Box 9, Folder 151.7)
  - Two men shaking hands, undated (Box 9, Folder 151.8)
  - Two men and a woman having a conversation, undated (Box 9, Folder 151.9)
  - Two men and a woman having a conversation, undated (Box 9, Folder 151.1)
  - Two men and a woman having a conversation, undated (Box 9, Folder 151.11)
  - Negatives of the previous pictures, undated (Box 9, Folder 151.12)
  - A woman addresses an audience while men stand in background holding drinks, undated (Box 9, Folder 152.1)
  - A women addresses an audience while men stand in background holding drinks, undated (Box 9, Folder 152.2)
  - Two women posing one holding a drink, undated (Box 9, Folder 152.3)
  - Two women having a conversation, undated (Box 9, Folder 152.4)
  - Two women and a man posing for the camera, undated (Box 9, Folder 152.5)
  - 3 women posing for the camera, undated (Box 9, Folder 152.6)
  - 3 women posing for the camera, undated (Box 9, Folder 152.7)
  - Man addressing the audience, undated (Box 9, Folder 152.8)
  - Man addressing the audience, undated (Box 9, Folder 152.9)
  - Two men shaking hands, undated (Box 9, Folder 153.1)
  - Two men shaking hands, undated (Box 9, Folder 153.2)
  - Sheldon S. Cohen, Dean Swartz and others eating, undated (Box 9, Folder 153.3)
  - Two men talking to one another, undated (Box 9, Folder 153.4)
  - Pres. Trachenberg and other eating, undated (Box 9, Folder 153.5)
  - A man giving a speech, undated (Box 9, Folder 153.6)
  - Glickman, Friedenthal and an unidentified individ., undated (Box 9, Folder 154.1)
  - Freidenthal and two others conversating, undated (Box 9, Folder 154.2)
  - A man at podium giving a speech, undated (Box 9, Folder 154.3)
  - A man at podium giving a speech, undated (Box 9, Folder 154.4)
  - Rep. John Dyncan and a man conversating, undated (Box 9, Folder 155.1)
  - Rep. John Dyncan and a man conversating, undated (Box 9, Folder 155.2)
  - Rep. John Dyncan and a man conversating, undated (Box 9, Folder 155.3)
  - Rep. John Dyncan and a woman conversating, undated (Box 9, Folder 155.4)
  - Negatives of the previous pictures, undated (Box 9, Folder 155.5)
  - A man and a woman watching a presentaion, undated (Box 9, Folder 156.1)
  - Three men watching a presentaion, undated (Box 9, Folder 156.2)
  - A man and a woman conversating, undated (Box 9, Folder 156.3)
  - The head table at a dinner, undated (Box 9, Folder 156.4)
  - A table of men at a dinner, undated (Box 9, Folder 156.5)
  - A table of men at a dinner, undated (Box 9, Folder 156.6)
  - Prof. Jackson, undated (Box 9, Folder 156.7)
  - A table of people at a black tie dinner, undated (Box 9, Folder 157.1)
  - A man speaking at a podium, undated (Box 9, Folder 157.2)
  - A man speaking at a podium, undated (Box 9, Folder 157.3)
  - Two men and two women posing for the camera, undated (Box 9, Folder 157.4)
  - A group of people in tuxedos dancing, undated (Box 9, Folder 157.5)
  - A man speaking at a podium, undated (Box 9, Folder 157.6)
  - A man and a woman conversating, undated (Box 9, Folder 157.7)
  - Six men posing for a picture, undated (Box 9, Folder 157.8)
  - 3 men and a women conversating, undated (Box 9, Folder 157.9)
  - A man and a woman conversating, while two men and a woman pose for the camera, undated (Box 9, Folder 157.1)
  - A group of men and women pose for the camers, undated (Box 9, Folder 157.11)
  - A man and a woman shake hands, undated (Box 9, Folder 157.12)
  - A man and a woman pose for the picture, undated (Box 9, Folder 157.13)
  - Two men pose for a picture, undated (Box 9, Folder 157.14)
  - Two men pose for the camera, undated (Box 9, Folder 157.15)
  - Two men pose for the camera, undated (Box 9, Folder 157.16)
  - Negatives of the previous pictures, undated (Box 9, Folder 157.17)
  - NLC Centenial Anniversary Logo, undated (Box 9, Folder 158.1)
  - NLC Centenial Anniversary Logo, undated (Box 9, Folder 158.2)
  - NLC Centenial Anniversary Logo, undated (Box 9, Folder 158.3)
  - Patricia Curran, undated (Box 9, Folder 160)
  - Ronie Blumenthal, undated (Box 9, Folder 161)
  - C.L. Beaudoin, undated (Box 9, Folder 162)
  - Ira C. Eaker, undated (Box 9, Folder 163)
  - Patricia Cahill, undated (Box 9, Folder 164)
  - Edward B. Cohen, undated (Box 9, Folder 165)
  - Lorraine Chang, 11/1981 (Box 9, Folder 166)
  - John P. Edwards, undated (Box 9, Folder 167)
  - Gerald Eppner, undated (Box 9, Folder 168)
  - F.B. Henry, undated (Box 9, Folder 169)
  - Robert J. Fair, undated (Box 9, Folder 170)
  - Donald A. Rowe and others, undated (Box 9, Folder 171.1)
    [l. to r.] Tom Tarolli, Jim Watterson, Bert Mullholland, Chuck Rosenberg and David King
  - Donald A. Rowe and others, undated (Box 9, Folder 171.2)
    [l. to r.] Don Rowe, David King, Prof. David Weaver, and Al Brody
  - Maryland Chapter GWLA, MD State Bar Association, 01/04/1978 (Box 9, Folder 172.1)
    Dean Edward A. Potts, Arthur S. Field
  - Maryland Chapter GWLA, MD State Bar Association, 01/04/1978 (Box 9, Folder 172.2)
  - Maryland Chapter GWLA, MD State Bar Association, 01/04/1978 (Box 9, Folder 172.3)
    Jacob A. Stein speaks on the subject of Watergate
  - Maryland Chapter GWLA, MD State Bar Association, 01/04/1978 (Box 9, Folder 172.4)
    Judge Jacob S. Levine, Albert Ginsberg, Wilbur Ross Hubbord, Ronald A. Willoner, Jacob A. Stein
  - Maryland Chapter GWLA, MD State Bar Association, 01/04/1978 (Box 9, Folder 172.5)
    Judge Levin, Albert Ginsberg, Wilber Ross Hubbord, Ronoald A. Willoner, Jacob A. Stein
  - Maryland Chapter GWLA, MD State Bar Association, 01/04/1978 (Box 9, Folder 172.6)
    Samuel W. H. Meloy, Ronald A. Willoner
  - Maryland Chapter GWLA, MD State Bar Association, 01/04/1978 (Box 9, Folder 172.7)
    Leon Jawarski, Jacob A. Stein, Cliff Doughtery, Dewey Sehade
  - Phoenix Alumni Dinner, undated (Box 9, Folder 173.1)
    Dr. Elliot, Jans Comos, a man and a woman
  - Phoenix Alumni Dinner, undated (Box 9, Folder 173.2)
  - Phoenix Alumni Dinner, undated (Box 9, Folder 173.3)
  - Phoenix Alumni Dinner, undated (Box 9, Folder 173.4)
  - Phoenix Alumni Dinner, undated (Box 9, Folder 173.5)
    Dean Kramer, Simon Yaffee and a man
  - Phoenix Alumni Dinner, undated (Box 9, Folder 173.6)
    A group of 10 men posing for the camera
  - Phoenix Alumni Dinner, undated (Box 9, Folder 173.7)
    Dr. Elliot conversating with Evelyn Jones Kirmse
  - Phoenix Alumni Dinner, undated (Box 9, Folder 173.8)
    Dean Kramer and Frank Parks
  - Law Alumni Newsletter Photos, 03/1978 (Box 10, Folder 174.1)
    Unidentified, four participants posing for a photo
  - Law Alumni Newsletter Photos, 03/1978 (Box 10, Folder 174.2)
    Five participants posing for a photo
  - Law Alumni Newsletter Photos, 03/1978 (Box 10, Folder 174.3)
  - Law Alumni Newsletter Photos, 03/1978 (Box 10, Folder 174.4)
    Crooler, Tunage, Skinner, Alembiah
  - Law Alumni Newsletter Photos, 03/1978 (Box 10, Folder 174.5)
    Two men shaking hands
  - Law Alumni Newsletter Photos, 03/1978 (Box 10, Folder 174.6)
    Mr. Stein juggling
  - Law Alumni Newsletter Photos, 03/1978 (Box 10, Folder 174.7)
    Chester A. Zyblut and other participants
  - Law Alumni Newsletter Photos, 03/1978 (Box 10, Folder 174.8)
    Dean Kramer, Mrs. Kramer, and Betty Ann Thompson
  - Law Alumni Newsletter Photos, 03/1978 (Box 10, Folder 174.9)
    Participants with refreshments
  - Law Alumni Newsletter Photos, 03/1978 (Box 10, Folder 174.1)
    Alexander W. Whitrer, Belva, D. Newseme, and Margret L. Hanes
  - Law Alumni Newsletter Photos, 03/1978 (Box 10, Folder 174.11)
    Pres. Elliot honoring a participant
  - Law Alumni Newsletter Photos, 03/1978 (Box 10, Folder 174.12)
    Group of particpants
  - Law Alumni Newsletter Photos, 03/1978 (Box 10, Folder 174.13)
    Pres. Elliot honoring Marion Edwin Harrison
  - Law Alumni Newsletter Photos, 03/1978 (Box 10, Folder 174.14)
    James S. Reid, Mrs. Reid, and Ellwood Smith
  - Law Alumni Newsletter Photos, 03/1978 (Box 10, Folder 174.15)
    Participants chatting
  - Law Alumni Newsletter Photos, 03/1978 (Box 10, Folder 174.16)
    Charles L. Mariuaccio and two female participants
  - Law Alumni Newsletter Photos, 03/1978 (Box 10, Folder 174.17)
    Robert Visser, Heleen Pachter, and other participant
  - Law Alumni Newsletter Photos, 01/1978 (Box 10, Folder 175)
    Rowland F. Kirks
  - Law Alumni Newsletter Photos, undated (Box 10, Folder 176)
    M. Cherif Bassiouni
  - Law Alumni Newsletter Photos, undated (Box 10, Folder 177)
    Orlando Seminar
  - Law Alumni Newsletter Photos, undated (Box 10, Folder 178)
    St. Petersburg Seminar particpants
  - Law Alumni Newsletter Photos, undated (Box 10, Folder 179)
    President Elliot presenting GW bust to a participant
  - Law Alumni Newsletter Photos, undated (Box 10, Folder 180)
    A group of participants
  - Oct. 1981 Law Alumni Newsletter Photos, 08/11/1981 (Box 10, Folder 181.1)
    Participants, ABA New Orleans
  - Oct. 1981 Law Alumni Newsletter Photos, 08/11/1981 (Box 10, Folder 181.2)
  - Oct. 1981 Law Alumni Newsletter Photos, undated (Box 10, Folder 181.3)
    ZBA Breakfast, Denver, Colorado
  - Oct. 1981 Law Alumni Newsletter Photos, 07/27/1981 (Box 10, Folder 181.4)
    Prof. Pock, Debbie Malinsky, Robert R. Vawler at a reception, Florida
  - Oct. 1981 Law Alumni Newsletter Photos, undated (Box 10, Folder 181.5)
    Joseph E. Szbabo and Laurence R. Pretty
  - Oct. 1981 Law Alumni Newsletter Photos, 06/12/1981 (Box 10, Folder 181.6)
    Fred W. Bannett, Bruce Lipstein and another male participant
  - Oct. 1981 Law Alumni Newsletter Photos, 06/12/1981 (Box 10, Folder 181.7)
  - Oct. 1981 Law Alumni Newsletter Photos (Box 10, Folder 181.8)
    Dean Barron presents the prize money to the 1980-81 upperclass winners of the Van Vleck Moot Court, William P. Tedesco and Sally Ann Hostetler
  - Oct. 1981 Law Alumni Newsletter Photos, 02/25/1981 (Box 10, Folder 181.9)
    Judge Thomas L. Camp, Aaron I. Alembik, and Dr. Jonas Robitscher at the Coffee and Dessert Reception of the GWU Law Alumni Association
  - Feb. 1981 Law Alumni Newsletter [unused photos], 10/11/1980 (Box 10, Folder 182.1)
    Whitcomb, Myra Barron, Lucero Barron, and Judge Campbell, GWLA Breakfast, Colorado Bar Association MTG.
  - Feb. 1981 Law Alumni Newsletter [unused photos], undated (Box 10, Folder 182.2)
    Dr. Milton E. Mermestein, Dr. Jacob Burns, Robert D. Krumme, Howard P. Hoffman at the Krumme reception
  - Feb. 1981 Law Alumni Newsletter [unused photos], 10/02/1980 (Box 10, Folder 182.3)
    M. Byron Fisherand Dean Barron chatting after the Salt Lake City Luncheon
  - Feb. 1981 Law Alumni Newsletter [unused photos], 10/18/1980 (Box 10, Folder 182.4)
    David Shapiro and Veron R. Todd at the Annualmeeting of the Sun Coast Chapter of the General Alumni Association
  - Feb. 1981 Law Alumni Newsletter [unused photos], undated (Box 10, Folder 182.5)
    Marshall C. Gardner, Mrs. Gardner, and William P. Smith
  - Feb. 1981 Law Alumni Newsletter [unused photos], undated (Box 10, Folder 182.6)
    Ann Fryer, William T. Fryer III, Mary Fryer, Mary Lee Fryer, Prof. Glen E. Weston, Prof. S. Chesterfield Oppenhein, Betty Fryer
  - Feb. 1981 Law Alumni Newsletter [unused photos], undated (Box 10, Folder 182.7)
    Judy Dobbins, Dean Jerome A. Barron, and Allen T. Eaton
  - July 1977 Law Alumni Newsletter Photos, undated (Box 10, Folder 183.1)
    Four men participants, folder labeled 183 A
  - July 1977 Law Alumni Newsletter Photos, undated (Box 10, Folder 183.2)
    A group of men participants, folder labeled 183 A
  - July 1977 Law Alumni Newsletter Photos, undated (Box 10, Folder 183.3)
  - July 1977 Law Alumni Newsletter Photos, undated (Box 10, Folder 183.4)
    Pres. Elliot and Dean Kramer with another participant in Los Angeles, folder labeled 183 A
  - July 1977 Law Alumni Newsletter Photos, undated (Box 10, Folder 183.5)
    Pres. Eliot and Dean Kramer with another participant in Los Angles, folder labeled 183 A
  - July 1977 Law Alumni Newsletter Photos, undated (Box 10, Folder 183.6)
    Four participants, folder labeled 183 A
  - July 1977 Law Alumni Newsletter Photos, undated (Box 10, Folder 183.7)
    Pres. Elliot, Dean Kramer, and other participants in san Francisco, folder labeled 183 A
  - July 1977 Law Alumni Newsletter Photos, 04/11/1977 (Box 10, Folder 183.8)
    Dean Kramer and other paticipants in Seattle, folder labeled 183 A
  - July 1977 Law Alumni Newsletter Photos, 04/11/1977 (Box 10, Folder 183.9)
    Pres. Elliot Dean Kramer and other paticipants in San Diego, folder labeled 183 A
  - July 1977 Law Alumni Newsletter Photos, 04/11/1977 (Box 10, Folder 183.1)
    Three men participants posing for a photo, folder labeled 183 A
  - July 1977 Law Alumni Newsletter Photos, 04/11/1977 (Box 10, Folder 183.11)
    Two male alumni of 1917 and 1927, folder labeled 183 A
  - July 1977 Law Alumni Newsletter Photos, 04/11/1977 (Box 10, Folder 183.12)
    Dean Kramer and a female participant at the dining table, folder labeled 183 A
  - July 1977 Law Alumni Newsletter Photos, 04/11/1977 (Box 10, Folder 183.13)
    A speaker and an audience, folder labeled 183 A
  - July 1977 Law Alumni Newsletter Photos, 04/11/1977 (Box 10, Folder 183.14)
    Pres. Elliot with four men participants, folder labeled 183 A
  - July 1977 Law Alumni Newsletter Photos, 04/11/1977 (Box 10, Folder 183.15)
    Dean Kramer with other participants, folder labeled 183 A
  - July 1977 Law Alumni Newsletter Photos, 04/11/1977 (Box 10, Folder 183.16)
    Three women chatting, folder labeled 183 A
  - July 1977 Law Alumni Newsletter Photos, 04/11/1977 (Box 10, Folder 183.17)
    Hon. Godfrey L. Monter and two other participants, folder labeled 183 A
  - July 1977 Law Alumni Newsletter Photos, undated (Box 10, Folder 183.18)
    Joseph A. DePaul and other participants, folder labeled 183 A
  - July 1977 Law Alumni Newsletter Photos, undated (Box 10, Folder 183.19)
    Hon. Jack S. Levin and another paticipant, folder labeled 183 A
  - July 1977 Law Alumni Newsletter Photos, undated (Box 10, Folder 183.2)
    Ron Willoner with another participant, folder labeled 183 A
  - July 1977 Law Alumni Newsletter Photos, undated (Box 10, Folder 183.21)
    Two couples with refreshments, folder labeled 183 A
  - July 1977 Law Alumni Newsletter Photos, 07/1977 (Box 10, Folder 183.22)
    Pres. Elliot chatting with a participant, folder labeled 183 B, item #1
  - July 1977 Law Alumni Newsletter Photos, 07/1977 (Box 10, Folder 183.23)
    A speaker and participants at the New York Hilton, folder labeled 183 B, item #2
  - July 1977 Law Alumni Newsletter Photos, 07/1977 (Box 10, Folder 183.24)
    A speaker and participants at the New York Hilton, folder labeled 183 B, item #3
  - July 1977 Law Alumni Newsletter Photos, 07/1977 (Box 10, Folder 183.25)
    Three participants chatting, folder labeled 183 B, item #4
  - July 1977 Law Alumni Newsletter Photos, 07/1977 (Box 10, Folder 183.26)
    Three participants chatting, folder labeled 183 B, item #5
  - July 1977 Law Alumni Newsletter Photos, 07/1977 (Box 10, Folder 183.27)
    Pres. Elliot displaying medals accompanied by other participants, folder labeled 183 B, item #6
  - July 1977 Law Alumni Newsletter Photos, 07/1977 (Box 10, Folder 183.28)
    A group of participants, folder labeled 183 B, item #7
  - July 1977 Law Alumni Newsletter Photos, 07/1977 (Box 10, Folder 183.29)
    Pres. Elliot with Dean Kramer, Mrs. Elliot and Peter R. [?], folder labeled 183 B, item #8
  - July 1977 Law Alumni Newsletter Photos, 07/1977 (Box 10, Folder 183.3)
    Pres. Elliot, Dean Kramer, and two other individuals in grauduation gowns, folder labeled 183 B, item #9
  - July 1977 Law Alumni Newsletter Photos, 07/1977 (Box 10, Folder 183.31)
    Harris, Stein Whitalia at D.C. chapter luncheon, folder labeled 183 B, item #10
  - July 1977 Law Alumni Newsletter Photos, 07/1977 (Box 10, Folder 183.32)
    Dean Kramer, David Lee, and Pres. Elliot chatting, folder labeled 183 B, item #11
  - July 1977 Law Alumni Newsletter Photos, 07/1977 (Box 10, Folder 183.33)
    Charles B. Philips greeting a female participant, folder labeled 183 B, item #12
  - July 1977 Law Alumni Newsletter Photos, 07/1977 (Box 10, Folder 183.34)
    Steve R. [?], D. Weaver, and a female, folder labeled 183 B, item #13
  - July 1977 Law Alumni Newsletter Photos, 07/1977 (Box 10, Folder 183.35)
    Pres. Elliot and another man in graduation gowns with the GW bust, folder labeled 183 B, item #14
  - July 1977 Law Alumni Newsletter Photos, 07/1977 (Box 10, Folder 183.36)
    Two men chatting, folder labeled 183 B, item #15
  - July 1977 Law Alumni Newsletter Photos, undated (Box 10, Folder 183.37)
    Donald C. Cook with his award and two others, folder labeled 183 B, item #16
  - July 1977 Law Alumni Newsletter Photos, 10/1976 (Box 10, Folder 183.38)
    Richard Kramer with his award and two other men, folder labeled 183 B, item #17
  - Oct. 1976 Law Alumni Newsletter Photos, 10/1976 (Box 10, Folder 184.1)
    Two couples posing for a photo
  - Oct. 1976 Law Alumni Newsletter Photos, 10/1976 (Box 10, Folder 184.2)
    William C. Miller, Charles D. Award, and two men with their awards
  - Oct. 1976 Law Alumni Newsletter Photos, 10/1976 (Box 10, Folder 184.3)
    John C. Menett, Louis D. Nattkemper, Pres. Elliot Lester M. Ponder, and Richard D. Gilory
  - Oct. 1976 Law Alumni Newsletter Photos, 10/1976 (Box 10, Folder 184.4)
    Dean Kramer greeting a female
  - Oct. 1976 Law Alumni Newsletter Photos, 10/1976 (Box 10, Folder 184.5)
    A group re-enacting the civil war army
  - Oct. 1976 Law Alumni Newsletter Photos, 10/1976 (Box 10, Folder 184.6)
    Two men and a women chatting
  - Oct. 1976 Law Alumni Newsletter Photos, 10/1976 (Box 10, Folder 184.7)
    Speakers by the podium
  - Oct. 1976 Law Alumni Newsletter Photos, 10/1976 (Box 10, Folder 184.8)
    A speaker addressing an audience
  - Oct. 1976 Law Alumni Newsletter Photos, 10/1976 (Box 10, Folder 184.9)
  - Oct. 1976 Law Alumni Newsletter Photos, 10/1976 (Box 10, Folder 184.1)
    Hon. Mark White, George Goodwin, Lou Nora Spiller, William F. Kemp
  - Oct. 1976 Law Alumni Newsletter Photos, 10/1976 (Box 10, Folder 184.11)
    Judge Lawerence S. Margolis, US Mugistrate for the District of Columbia